checkspeedtab.com 2018-10-14

# Privacy Policy

**Hopebest** provides this Privacy Policy to demonstrate our commitment to respecting and protecting your privacy. This Privacy Policy applies to the Hopebest suite of softwares. Our privacy policy describes your rights regarding our use of your personal information. 

Search Services   
Our search applications be used as your browser homepage when we implement the search functionality through the browser settings. The default search features can be disabled by removing the files that you downloaded from the HopeBest Products. 

Information We Collect    
We collect personal information in order to provide you with a better use of Hopebest. Anonymous information such as the number of your link clicks, page views, and login times may also be collected to help us enhance your overall experience. We may store your personal information in an aggregate format or in an identifiable format. 

How We Collect Information 

**Information You Provide to Us.**  When you use Hopebest services, we may collect information provided to us when you post to the Hopebest in another manner. When you log-in to the HOPEBEST Services via Facebook or another social media platform, we may also collect the information provided to us through these sites. When we provide you with an email inbox, we may collect and monitor the contents of emails sent through the system. 

**Storage of Information Provided**   
When you use Hopebest services, our service requires you to upload/download a file to our server to check your Internet speed. We do not store your speed check results and all internet speed check results are deleted within 1 hour.

**Automatically Captured Information.**  We automatically collect information sent to us by your operating device when you use the HOPEBEST Services. The information sent to us may include your IP address, data about the pages you access, mobile network information, search history, and a time-stamp. Through the content of our undeleted cookies, we may also collect information regarding the devices connected to your computer, software installed upon, and referring website addresses. 

**Other Technologies:**  We may also collect and store information through our use of cookies and web beacons to help provide you with a better and safer experience with our HOPEBEST Services. Web beacons are small graphic images that may be embedded in images on our site to customize the services we offer to our users. 

Information Collected By Third-Parties And Behavioral Advertising    
**On the HOPEBEST Services:**  We may also obtain information about you from third parties such as our authorized service providers, advertising companies, and HOPEBEST affiliates. In order to gather information about users who interact with their advertisements, these companies may use cookies to monitor clicks. 

**On Third Party Sites, Services, And Applications.**  The Hopebest family of companies correspond with advertisers, data management platform, and ad networks to customize online behavioral advertisements that are created to target users' interests. In order to deliver these advertisements, these third parties may and/or we may disclose to these third parties an identification number to be associated with your device's platform. 

How We Use the Information We Collect   
Our primary goal in collecting information is to provide you with a safe and customized user experience. We may use your personal information to: 

How We Share Your Information With Third Parties   
We may share your non-personal information we collect from you with others as indicated below: 

How We Protect and Store Personal Information   
The information that we collected may be stored and processed in the country or territory of Hong Kong. Regardless of the residence of your home country, we protect the information transferred in accordance with this Privacy Policy. We protect your information using physical, electronic, and procedural security measures. 

Third Party Websites   
When you click on a link in the HOPEBEST Service, you may be directed to third party websites. You can consult these third party websites for their Privacy Policy. 

How To Change Your Personal Information   
You may exercise your right to object our use of your personal information by writing to us at the below address support@checkspeedtab.com.  

Removal of Personal Information  
If you do not want us to retain or use your personal information in any way, please withdraw your consent (i.e. “opt out”), by contacting us at support@checkspeedtab.com.  

Questions about this Privacy Policy  
If you have any queries about this Privacy Policy or wish to resume receiving information which you may have previously opted-out of receiving, please contact us at support@checkspeedtab.com

Children's Privacy   
Our HOPEBEST Services are designed for those who are at least 13 years old. 

Notice of Changes To This Privacy Policy   
In the event that we create new HOPEBEST Products and Services that require additional privacy disclosure, we will update this Privacy Policy to support our revised business practices.
